那么现在麦蒂去剥树皮吃了
So while maddie's off skinning lunch...
我们干嘛不来叙叙旧呢
Why don't we catch up?
布丽  你不跟我说一下就来
Bree, it is so good of you to come
协助丽芙真是太好了
And support Liv on such short notice.
好的  凯伦
Well, karen,
当我的电视里的女儿打来电话
When my tv daughter called,
我就立马放下手头的一切赶来了
I just canceled everything on my schedule to be here.
也就是那些值得我
Just one of those situations
搭个做老娘的架子的事
Where I had to drop a butt bomb of mom on it.
搭个做老娘的架子
"drop a butt bomb of mom on it"
曾经是我的口头禅
Is something I used to say.
布丽听见了  结果就给她的电视角色抢去了
Bree heard it and turned it into her tv character's catchphrase.
自从那时  她就靠这发大财了
Since then, she's made a fortune
给烹饪书搭了个做老娘的架子
Dropping a butt bomb of mom on cookbooks,
锻炼视频  和让你青春永驻的酸奶
Workout videos, and yogurt that keeps you young.
我就此没有用过这句话
I haven't said it since.
好怀念啊
I really miss the butt bomb.
那么  妈妈
Well, mom--
- 咋了  亲爱的  - 啥事  甜心
- yeah, sugar? - what, sweetie?
噢...
Oh...
噢  天啊
Oh, wow!
这还真是尴尬啊  对不
This is awkward, isn't it?
我怎么没想到呢  呵呵
Hadn't really thought of that. ha ha!
之后我们要去搭帐篷
So we should probably go set up our tent.
然后我们在篝火边上见吧  凯伦女士
And I'll see you around the campfire, Karen?